<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">

	<!-- &lt;b> -->
	<!-- &lt;/b> -->

	<string-array name="whats_new_items" tools:ignore="InconsistentArrays">
		<item>12.6.0-beta</item>
		<item>Added &lt;b>timer&lt;/b>.</item>
		<item>Added &lt;b>repeat&lt;/b> options in alarm settings. Can repeat an alarm by hours, days, weeks, or months.</item>
		<item>Added &lt;b>date&lt;/b> option to have an alarm run on a particular date.  Accessible when selecting a time.</item>
		<item>Added &lt;b>snooze&lt;/b> with &lt;b>volume buttons&lt;/b>.</item>
		<item>Added &lt;b>dismiss NFC tags&lt;/b> in &lt;b>order&lt;/b> if multiple NFC tags are selected.  Can be dismissed in any, random, or sequential order.</item>
		<item>Added &lt;b>dismiss early notification&lt;/b>. Optionally show a notification when an alarm can be dismissed early.</item>
		<item>Added &lt;b>long press&lt;/b> on the repeat, vibrate, NFC, and flashlight buttons to quickly access those options.</item>
		<item>Fixed issue where playing all the &lt;b>music&lt;/b> in a &lt;b>folder&lt;/b> did not work.</item>
		<item>Updated to support &lt;b>Android 15&lt;/b>.</item>
		<item>Updated to support Android\'s &lt;b>Material 3&lt;/b> theme.</item>
		<item>12.5.4</item>
		<item>Fixed issue where &lt;b>skip next alarm&lt;/b> would keep skipping the alarm.</item>
		<item>12.5.3</item>
		<item>Fixed issue with &lt;b>voice&lt;/b> where text-to-speech was using the default voice even though a different voice was selected.</item>
		<item>Added &lt;b>alignment&lt;/b> option to the &lt;b>widget&lt;/b> to align all text.</item>
		<item>Added &lt;b>position&lt;/b> option to the &lt;b>widget&lt;/b> to position the alarm text.</item>
		<item>Added &lt;b>only show app alarms&lt;/b> option to the &lt;b>widget&lt;/b> which controls whether only alarms created in this app will be shown, or alarms created in any app will be shown.</item>
		<item>Added information on the &lt;b>remaining number of snoozes&lt;/b> when swiping to snooze an active alarm.</item>
		<item>Updated look of the &lt;b>What\'s New&lt;/b> dialog.</item>
		<item>12.5.2</item>
		<item>Added feature to &lt;b>select multiple NFC tags&lt;/b> that can dismiss an alarm.</item>
		<item>Added &lt;b>speech rate&lt;/b> to text-to-speech option to change the speed that it will speak.</item>
		<item>Fixed an issue with &lt;b>flashlight&lt;/b> where, when blink was disabled, it would still blink.</item>
		<item>12.5.0</item>
		<item>Updated &lt;b>alarm card&lt;/b> look to show buttons for dismiss options, snooze options, and regular alarm options.</item>
		<item>Added &lt;b>custom vibration pattern&lt;/b> option for alarms.</item>
		<item>Added &lt;b>battery saver&lt;/b> option to keep the screen off when an alarm is active. Found in Settings > General.</item>
		<item>Added &lt;b>voice&lt;/b> option to &lt;b>text-to-speech&lt;/b> to choose which voice to use.</item>
	</string-array>

</resources>
